<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yana on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/authors/yana/</link><description>Recent content in Yana on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:33:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/authors/yana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</guid><description>The importance of feedback Human beings are social by nature. Our inclination to change our behavior in reliance upon feedback from our fellows is a primary evolutionary adaptation mechanism. Feedback is our relationship with the world and the world’s relationship with us, it’s how we make an impact on other people. Working in co-located environments, we are accustomed to making evaluations based on verbal and non-verbal signals: body language, tone of voice, facial expression, and many more.</description></item><item><title>Onboarding</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</guid><description>The first few months are crucial to the success of the new hire. The newcomer will either buy in by investing their time and attention or treat the company as a paycheck printer, working hard enough not to get fired.
Buddies help to make onboarding experience engaging, yet well-organized and structured. Work-related information, served in tiny bits in the issue-tracker, facilitates the smooth transition to work culture of a Hygge company.</description></item><item><title>Staying Social</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</guid><description>Distributed teams need to work together and communicate intensively. Work is always easier when you know the person you’re communicating with. That’s why Hygge Companies not only encourage personal interactions during team calls, meetups, and workations but also organize Hygge Roulette to foster interpersonal communication.
Team calls Working remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean working alone. To keep everyone involved, Hygge Companies have regular calls where team members share their work and lives. Before the call, the team leads prepare a slide to talk about the progress of their products and milestones.</description></item><item><title>Personal Project</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-project/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-project/</guid><description>Every newcomer&amp;rsquo;s journey at Hygge Company starts with a personal project. Personal project is a private space to set and track personal milestones. It can take different forms - personal repository or a dashboard, depends on an issue tracker that Hygge company uses.
Enjoy making daily to-do lists? Want to test how markdown on GitHub works? Planning to learn Python from a colleague? Personal project is a powerful tool that satisfies all those needs.</description></item><item><title>Sisu</title><link>https://hygge.work/sisu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/sisu/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire certain types of people: the selection process is designed to spot talented people who are passionate about what they do and ready to hustle to achieve their goals, both personal and professional.
In remote settings, Hygge employees have to learn to manage their resources and energy in a new way. This is why Hygge Companies adopt the concept of good daily sisu to keep their people going.</description></item><item><title>Buddy guidelines</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</guid><description>Visiting another country or hiking an unknown trail all by yourself definitely has its advantages. But if you want to get to know all the local tips and tricks, discover the best view-points and learn fast and safe ways up, you look for local guides.
The same is when you join a new team. A new employee’s onboarding experience is greatly enhanced by buddy who acts as a local guide. It is a person to show around, share advice regarding day-to-day work at Hygge company.</description></item><item><title>Attention Management</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no one to tell you how to organize your day and prioritize important things. Try attention management instead of time management and use time-saving tools and shortcuts.
Priorities Rules, guidelines, principles, people, they all have influence on what you do and how you do it. How do you figure out who to listen to and what to prioritize? Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of things to consider in the order of their importance:</description></item><item><title>Planning</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</guid><description>Have a plan. However bad it might be. It&amp;rsquo;s much better to come up with a numbered steps plan and ask people to help you to improve it than make them guess or create one for you.
Have trouble making a plan? Try Goal Breakdown Having a big goal with many time-consuming steps can be very stressful or overwhelming. The bigger your destination, the higher the chance you will start &amp;ldquo;tomorrow&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;next week.</description></item><item><title>Google Workspace</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/google-workspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/google-workspace/</guid><description>Google Workspace is the professional version of Gmail, Calendar, Meet, Docs, Team Drive, and much more. It provides great functionality that covers Hygge companies&amp;rsquo; need in access management, planning and working. A corporate Google account not only grants access to that whole ecosystem but also serves as the key to other web applications. The world where you needed to create separate accounts with unique passwords for each application is fading away.</description></item><item><title>Corporate chats</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/chats/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/chats/</guid><description>Hygge Companies stick to asynchronous communication. This means that out of all the communication channels, they choose those where people don’t have to be present at the same time or in the same space, either physically or virtually.
However, some team-building interactions are meant to be synchronous, such as company chats. Element and Signal are good examples of secure chats. They are great team-building tools that enable water cooler-like conversations and calls.</description></item><item><title>Navigating Change: Reset plan after Layoff</title><link>https://hygge.work/layoff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/layoff/</guid><description>Losing your job can feel like stepping into the unknown, and it&amp;rsquo;s completely normal to feel disoriented. Suddenly, the familiar routines, work buddies, and daily grind are gone, and it&amp;rsquo;s okay to feel a bit lost. But hey, this period can also be a chance for personal and professional growth.
If you find yourself facing a layoff, here are some friendly tips to help you transition smoothly and come out even stronger on the other side:</description></item><item><title>Remote Job Hunt: Find killer remote gigs</title><link>https://hygge.work/remotejob/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remotejob/</guid><description>Are you on a quest to discover the remote job of your dreams? Look no further! In this curated list of job-seeking websites, we&amp;rsquo;ve gathered the best platforms to help you land those killer remote gigs. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and discover the opportunities waiting for you!
300 Global Companies with Eastern European roots WorkingNomads Letsworkremotely Otta RemoteOk Vc GeekJob Weworkremotely FlexJobs Remotive Tealhq JustRemote</description></item><item><title>Building Deeper Connections with Others</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/in-depth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/in-depth/</guid><description>In a fast-paced world filled with distractions and superficial interactions, engaging in meaningful conversations has become a rare occurrence. With colleagues, family, friends, and even strangers, the ability to engage in deep, authentic conversations is a skill worth honing. Meaningful conversations not only foster stronger relationships but also provide opportunities for personal growth and understanding. Here are some tips to help you cultivate meaningful conversations in various aspects of your life.</description></item><item><title>Communication: How culture shapes our perception</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/cross-cultural/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/cross-cultural/</guid><description>Cross-cultural differences are a common challenge in the tech industry. As companies operate in a global environment, they must be aware of fundamental cultural differences to promote better communication and collaboration among employees from different cultures, and ensure that business deals and transactions with other global partners go smoothly. Challenges can arise as a result of any differences that multicultural companies might face in the following areas:
Communication styles Attitudes toward conflict Approaches to completing tasks Decision-making styles Attitudes toward disclosure Approaches to knowing Understanding and navigating these cultural differences is key to building successful relationships with colleagues and clients from different backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>Creating value for your remote team</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/anchors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/anchors/</guid><description>Being an effective remote manager is tricky. You have to find the right leadership style that corresponds to your personal values, take care of your team, and make sure that you hit the goals that are important for the business.
When juggling between all the tasks you have on your plate when leading a remote workforce, it’s important to pay attention to the things that are important for the people you manage.</description></item><item><title>Leading a team remotely</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/leading/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/leading/</guid><description>How to make work a better place for your virtual team While all of us come to work every day for various reasons, there are several universal things that make remote work better. In remote teams, leaders have the opportunity to create an environment in which a team can flourish by building a sense of competency, autonomy, and relatedness for everyone. When people feel that they are competent in what they are doing, that they have a choice of tasks and independence, and that somebody at work cares about them, they feel happier, grow better professionally, and feel more engaged with their jobs.</description></item><item><title>Managing team members based on their competency levels</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/situational-leadership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/situational-leadership/</guid><description>Situational leadership and how to use it in onboarding and day-to-day team management
Leadership is not a one-size-fits-all approach. A leader comes across various types of people and situations, and that’s where situational leadership comes into the picture—it’s all about tailoring your leadership style to fit the situation and the competency level of your team members.
When it comes to leadership styles, there are four main types: directing, coaching, supporting, and delegating.</description></item><item><title>Level Up Your LinkedIn Game</title><link>https://hygge.work/linkedin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/linkedin/</guid><description>Whether you&amp;rsquo;re actively seeking a new opportunity or just want to stay connected in the professional world, one platform stands out as a valuable ally in your journey – LinkedIn. Your LinkedIn profile is not just an online resume; it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful tool that can help you stand out in the digital crowd and pave the way for exciting career prospects.
LinkedIn, often dubbed the world&amp;rsquo;s largest online networking platform, connects job seekers, hiring managers, and businesses alike.</description></item></channel></rss>