<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MarketCapBot: Challenge Program Use Case</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/marketcapbot-challenge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/marketcapbot-challenge/</guid><description>Task-performance based selection is the future for tech companies. That is why Hygge companies use the Challenge Program to provide candidates an opportunity to demonstrate their skills in real-life scenarios and to experience what their work might be like before making the decision to stick with the company.
Some issues in the Challenge Program have the bounty label. These are one-off paid tasks that usually require advanced skills. How do Hygge companies come up with these tasks?</description></item><item><title>Github Project Boards: Begginer-friendly Guide to Self/Team Management</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/project-boards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/project-boards/</guid><description>GitHub might be seen as a platform just for coding, but it also offers a broad range of task tracking tools that can benefit both personal and team projects. Hygge companies love using GitHub because it helps keeping everyone on the same page, managing tasks, and ensuring everyone meets their deadlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at some examples of personal and team dashboards.
The personal dashboard is super user-friendly and allows you to customize it with features that are perfect for your unique needs.</description></item><item><title>Creating value for your remote team</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/anchors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/anchors/</guid><description>Being an effective remote manager is tricky. You have to find the right leadership style that corresponds to your personal values, take care of your team, and make sure that you hit the goals that are important for the business.
When juggling between all the tasks you have on your plate when leading a remote workforce, it’s important to pay attention to the things that are important for the people you manage.</description></item><item><title>Leading a team remotely</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/leading/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/leading/</guid><description>How to make work a better place for your virtual team While all of us come to work every day for various reasons, there are several universal things that make remote work better. In remote teams, leaders have the opportunity to create an environment in which a team can flourish by building a sense of competency, autonomy, and relatedness for everyone. When people feel that they are competent in what they are doing, that they have a choice of tasks and independence, and that somebody at work cares about them, they feel happier, grow better professionally, and feel more engaged with their jobs.</description></item><item><title>Managing team members based on their competency levels</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/situational-leadership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/situational-leadership/</guid><description>Situational leadership and how to use it in onboarding and day-to-day team management
Leadership is not a one-size-fits-all approach. A leader comes across various types of people and situations, and that’s where situational leadership comes into the picture—it’s all about tailoring your leadership style to fit the situation and the competency level of your team members.
When it comes to leadership styles, there are four main types: directing, coaching, supporting, and delegating.</description></item><item><title>How to plan a company retreat</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/workation-how-to/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/workation-how-to/</guid><description>One of the most efficient ways to make people feel cozy and cared for is to arrange a great company retreat, or workation for them. It&amp;rsquo;s a sort of holiday event for a remote team where people get together in a beautiful place to hang out and work side by side.
We believe that workations are the best type of in-person gatherings for remote teams. They serve as a form of first aid for fully-distributed teams to heal all sorts of communication, intercultural, and work-related issues.</description></item><item><title>Personal Banking</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/personal-banking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/personal-banking/</guid><description>Hygge Companies view their employees as responsible adults who can manage not only their work, but also their money. Recent advancements in financial technology brought alternatives to the traditional consumer banking landscape. One way to visualize the key elements of this landscape is imagining a map of interconnected islands where legacy cash-based world borders gen Z contactless payment communities. Although much more complex in reality, this map gives general overview of basic services you can use to receive, store, and spend money anywhere in the world.</description></item><item><title>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/hygge-benefits/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/hygge-benefits/</guid><description>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks Well-thought benefits packages help Hygge companies retain their top-talents. In this post we shed some light on benefits that Inca Digital offers to their employees.
Effective remote work Being Hygge company, Incas don&amp;rsquo;t track the vacation days and time-off. Incas compensation remains the same even when they are off work for a while, as they don’t get paid for their presence, but for the accomplished tasks.</description></item></channel></rss>