<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Personal Banking</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/personal-banking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/personal-banking/</guid><description>Hygge Companies view their employees as responsible adults who can manage not only their work, but also their money. Recent advancements in financial technology brought alternatives to the traditional consumer banking landscape. One way to visualize the key elements of this landscape is imagining a map of interconnected islands where legacy cash-based world borders gen Z contactless payment communities. Although much more complex in reality, this map gives general overview of basic services you can use to receive, store, and spend money anywhere in the world.</description></item><item><title>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/hygge-benefits/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/hygge-benefits/</guid><description>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks Well-thought benefits packages help Hygge companies retain their top-talents. In this post we shed some light on benefits that Inca Digital offers to their employees.
Effective remote work Being Hygge company, Incas don&amp;rsquo;t track the vacation days and time-off. Incas compensation remains the same even when they are off work for a while, as they don’t get paid for their presence, but for the accomplished tasks.</description></item><item><title>How to plan a company retreat</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/workation-how-to/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/workation-how-to/</guid><description>One of the most efficient ways to make people feel cozy and cared for is to arrange a great company retreat, or workation for them. It&amp;rsquo;s a sort of holiday event for a remote team where people get together in a beautiful place to hang out and work side by side.
We believe that workations are the best type of in-person gatherings for remote teams. They serve as a form of first aid for fully-distributed teams to heal all sorts of communication, intercultural, and work-related issues.</description></item></channel></rss>