<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marina on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/authors/marina/</link><description>Recent content in Marina on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 22:56:35 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/authors/marina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Issue Tracker</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/issue-tracker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/issue-tracker/</guid><description>There are plenty of Issue Trackers and Knowledge Management Systems out there to choose from. For the purpose of simplicity, we&amp;rsquo;ll use GitHub as an example of both. Anyone can set up a free personal (and even an organization) account and start building their Hygge Company using GitHub issue tracker and repositories for free!
Normally, Hygge Companies employees have set tasks and milestones with due dates for all of their projects.</description></item><item><title>Milestones</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</guid><description>Milestone is a SMART goal, that can be split into individual issues for steps and closed at the end of a sprint. It is not a place to collect thematically similar issues (project boards allow to organize your work in many different ways). Ideally, every milestone should be:
Specific – Well defined, clear, and unambiguous. A specific goal has a much greater chance of being accomplished than a general goal.</description></item><item><title>Pull Requests</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</guid><description>The pinnacle of mastering the async process is communicating through pull requests.
What is a pull request about?
Pull request is a tool for programmers to sustainably collaborate on code. In a larger context, pull request are useful for suggesting changes policies, wikis, and iteratively collaborating on complex documents. When companies are growing and changing, their approach to work also does: benefits, tools, and best practices are evolving. Before making a change, it&amp;rsquo;s always great to run your ideas by teammates and give others an opportunity to contribute to the final decision.</description></item></channel></rss>