<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ev on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/authors/ev/</link><description>Recent content in ev on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/authors/ev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Async</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</guid><description>To get things done, Hygge Companies rely on detailed documentation and atomic iterations that are visible to everyone through issue trackers like GitHub. Mastering this asynchronous workflow is vital to avoiding dysfunction. This is why Hygge companies prefer GitHub issues to chats and video calls. This also means that employees need to ensure that all conclusions made during offline conversations are recorded in GitHub, so that everyone at any time can follow your thought process.</description></item><item><title>Challenge Program</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</guid><description>The challenge program is a perfect tool for discovering hidden talent by autonomously vetting potential employees and interns at the start of the hiring process. The program consists of issues that can be solved without any access to company resources and require the participants to manage their own work. Such projects give interested individuals a chance to prove themselves, learn a bit about the company and products, and produce useful results in the process.</description></item><item><title>Peer Coaching</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</guid><description>Peer coaching is a form of learning and development where two team-members work together to reflect on current practices; expand, refine, and build new skills; share ideas; teach one another; or solve problems. It&amp;rsquo;s used in some Hygge Companies to improve internal communication and foster personal development of the team-members. These conversations rely on feedback giving and receiving skills.
Peer Coaching Policy Template Every 3 months (Jan 1, Apr 1, Jul 1, Oct 1) we devote some time to self-study and practice feedback during the peer coaching process.</description></item><item><title>Staying Social</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</guid><description>Distributed teams need to work together and communicate intensively. Work is always easier when you know the person you’re communicating with. That’s why Hygge Companies not only encourage personal interactions during team calls, meetups, and workations but also organize Hygge Roulette to foster interpersonal communication.
Team calls Working remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean working alone. To keep everyone involved, Hygge Companies have regular calls where team members share their work and lives.</description></item><item><title>Attention Management</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no one to tell you how to organize your day and prioritize important things. Try attention management instead of time management and use time-saving tools and shortcuts.
Priorities Rules, guidelines, principles, people, they all have influence on what you do and how you do it. How do you figure out who to listen to and what to prioritize? Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of things to consider in the order of their importance:</description></item><item><title>Planning</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</guid><description>Have a plan. However bad it might be. It&amp;rsquo;s much better to come up with a numbered steps plan and ask people to help you to improve it than make them guess or create one for you.
Have troubles making a plan? Try Goal Breakdown Having a big goal with many time-consuming steps can be very stressful, or even overwhelming. This is the type of goal that you will always start &amp;ldquo;tomorrow&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;next week&amp;rdquo;, but those times never seem to come.</description></item><item><title>Google Workspace</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/google-workspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/google-workspace/</guid><description>Google Workspace is the professional version of Gmail, Calendar, Meet, Docs, Team Drive, and much more. It provides great functionality that covers Hygge companies&amp;rsquo; need in access management, planning and working. A corporate Google account not only grants access to that whole ecosystem but also serves as the key to other web applications. The world where you needed to create separate accounts with unique passwords for each application is fading away.</description></item><item><title>Personal Growth</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire people not only because they are useful now, but also because they believe in their potential.
Working in a Hygge Company provides an opportunity for extremely efficient and, in many cases, very accelerated, career growth. In particular, it provides an opportunity to broaden your skill set well outside the narrow constraints that careers can have at most other companies. There is no red tape, allowing you to tailor your own “growth ladder”.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/security/</guid><description>Nothing will make you 100% safe. The goal is to make the attack prohibitively expensive. Below are the collection of simple tools and steps you can take to make yourself much safer.
To start, use dedicated devices for work or, at least, create a different user profile to isolate work resources from your personal account.
VPN Whether you live in a country that likes to filter traffic or just want to use non-secure WiFi networks, a good VPN is a must.</description></item><item><title>Personal Banking</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/personal-banking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/personal-banking/</guid><description>Hygge Companies view their employees as responsible adults who can manage not only their work, but also their money. Recent advancements in financial technology brought alternatives to the traditional consumer banking landscape. One way to visualize the key elements of this landscape is imagining a map of interconnected islands where legacy cash-based world borders gen Z contactless payment communities. Although much more complex in reality, this map gives general overview of basic services you can use to receive, store, and spend money anywhere in the world.</description></item></channel></rss>