<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hiring on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/tags/hiring/</link><description>Recent content in Hiring on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:33:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/tags/hiring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Challenge Program</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</guid><description>The challenge program is a perfect tool for discovering hidden talent by autonomously vetting potential employees and interns at the start of the hiring process. The program consists of issues that can be solved without any access to company resources and require the participants to manage their own work. Such projects give interested individuals a chance to prove themselves, learn a bit about the company and products, and produce useful results in the process.</description></item><item><title>Onboarding</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</guid><description>The first few months are crucial to the success of the new hire. The newcomer will either buy in by investing their time and attention or treat the company as a paycheck printer, working hard enough not to get fired.
Buddies help to make onboarding experience engaging, yet well-organized and structured. Work-related information, served in tiny bits in the issue-tracker, facilitates the smooth transition to work culture of a Hygge company.</description></item><item><title>MarketCapBot: Challenge Program Use Case</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/marketcapbot-challenge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/marketcapbot-challenge/</guid><description>Task-performance based selection is the future for tech companies. That is why Hygge companies use the Challenge Program to provide candidates an opportunity to demonstrate their skills in real-life scenarios and to experience what their work might be like before making the decision to stick with the company.
Some issues in the Challenge Program have the bounty label. These are one-off paid tasks that usually require advanced skills. How do Hygge companies come up with these tasks?</description></item></channel></rss>