<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Leading on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/tags/leading/</link><description>Recent content in Leading on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:13:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/tags/leading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Async</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</guid><description>To get things done, Hygge Companies rely on detailed documentation and atomic iterations that are visible to everyone through issue trackers like GitHub. Mastering this asynchronous workflow is vital to avoiding dysfunction. This is why Hygge companies prefer GitHub issues to chats and video calls. This also means that employees need to ensure that all conclusions made during offline conversations are recorded in GitHub, so that everyone at any time can follow your thought process.</description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</guid><description>The importance of feedback Human beings are social by nature. Our inclination to change our behavior in reliance upon feedback from our fellows is a primary evolutionary adaptation mechanism. Feedback is our relationship with the world and the world’s relationship with us, it’s how we make an impact on other people. Working in co-located environments, we are accustomed to making evaluations based on verbal and non-verbal signals: body language, tone of voice, facial expression, and many more.</description></item><item><title>Peer Coaching</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</guid><description>Peer coaching is a form of learning and development where two team-members work together to reflect on current practices; expand, refine, and build new skills; share ideas; teach one another; or solve problems. It&amp;rsquo;s used in some Hygge Companies to improve internal communication and foster personal development of the team-members. These conversations rely on feedback giving and receiving skills.
Peer Coaching Policy Template Every 3 months (Jan 1, Apr 1, Jul 1, Oct 1) we devote some time to self-study and practice feedback during the peer coaching process.</description></item><item><title>Staying Social</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</guid><description>Distributed teams need to work together and communicate intensively. Work is always easier when you know the person you’re communicating with. That’s why Hygge Companies not only encourage personal interactions during team calls, meetups, and workations but also organize Hygge Roulette to foster interpersonal communication.
Team calls Working remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean working alone. To keep everyone involved, Hygge Companies have regular calls where team members share their work and lives.</description></item><item><title>Buddy guidelines</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</guid><description>Visiting another country or hiking an unknown trail all by yourself definitely has its advantages. But if you want to get to know all the local tips and tricks, discover the best view-points and learn fast and safe ways up, you look for local guides.
The same is when you join a new team. A new employee’s onboarding experience is greatly enhanced by buddy who acts as a local guide.</description></item><item><title>Project Boards</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/project-boards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/project-boards/</guid><description>Having a helicopter view of your workflow offers numerous advantages. While focusing on individual tasks is important, the ability to step back and see the bigger picture allows for better strategic planning, resource allocation, and overall project management. This broader perspective not only enhances team efficiency but also contributes to personal professional growth.
Projects are a great way to manage GitHub workflow from a high-level perspective. They allow for comprehensive project management and task tracking, making it easier to oversee progress and collaborate effectively.</description></item><item><title>Attention Management</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no one to tell you how to organize your day and prioritize important things. Try attention management instead of time management and use time-saving tools and shortcuts.
Priorities Rules, guidelines, principles, people, they all have influence on what you do and how you do it. How do you figure out who to listen to and what to prioritize? Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of things to consider in the order of their importance:</description></item><item><title>Milestones</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</guid><description>Milestone is a SMART goal, that can be split into individual issues for steps and closed at the end of a sprint. It is not a place to collect thematically similar issues (project boards allow to organize your work in many different ways). Ideally, every milestone should be:
Specific – Well defined, clear, and unambiguous. A specific goal has a much greater chance of being accomplished than a general goal.</description></item><item><title>Planning</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</guid><description>Have a plan. However bad it might be. It&amp;rsquo;s much better to come up with a numbered steps plan and ask people to help you to improve it than make them guess or create one for you.
Have trouble making a plan? Try Goal Breakdown Having a big goal with many time-consuming steps can be very stressful or overwhelming. The bigger your destination, the higher the chance you will start &amp;ldquo;tomorrow&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;next week.</description></item><item><title>Growing</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/</guid><description>Hiring Hygge Companies believe in career choices guided by internal curiosity and the desire to do something meaningful. As intrinsic motivation seems to be one of the keys to happy remote work, Hygge Companies focus attract talent using Challenge and Bar Raiser programs to constantly evolve by hiring only the best people.
Typically, a selection process includes:
Job posting Challenge Submission Up to three interviews Hiring decision and onboarding</description></item><item><title>Personal Growth</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire people not only because they are useful now, but also because they believe in their potential.
Working in a Hygge Company provides an opportunity for extremely efficient and, in many cases, very accelerated, career growth. In particular, it provides an opportunity to broaden your skill set well outside the narrow constraints that careers can have at most other companies. There is no red tape, allowing you to tailor your own “growth ladder”.</description></item><item><title>Career development</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/career-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/career-development/</guid><description>Career development often implies performance surveys. However, there is a rule of a performance survey in Hygge companies: you don&amp;rsquo;t talk about the performance survey. Besides being a stressful experience for the employee being reviewed, filling out performance surveys is often an uncomfortable process for the reviewers and the managers who evaluate the results. Performance reviews often suffer from reviewer&amp;rsquo;s bias and might also lead to employee&amp;rsquo;s focus shift towards gaming the metrics instead of getting the job done.</description></item><item><title>Guiding Principles</title><link>https://hygge.work/guiding-principles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/guiding-principles/</guid><description>Take the initiative It will be difficult to understand how everything works by sitting quietly. There are no marching orders delivered to you on a daily basis, so the only sure way to figure things out is to take the initiative and to talk to people. Ask questions during calls, send messages in the company&amp;rsquo;s chat channels, and reach out to people outside your project for advice. Your colleagues have open calendars.</description></item><item><title>Embracing feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/embracing-feedback/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/embracing-feedback/</guid><description>This might be counterintuitive, but the receiver is in charge of feedback. They’re the one who decides what to listen to and how to make sense of it. That is why it is important for everyone to learn how to react to feedback. When you’re receiving praise, that’s usually easy; however, it might be hard to hold on your knee-jerk reaction and reject criticism. Try to do the following:
Assume positive intent.</description></item><item><title>Suggesting feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/suggesting-feedback/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/suggesting-feedback/</guid><description>insecure sharing corrective feedback. This is because people are scared of damaging the relationship, being wrong, losing face or hurting concerned individual. Studies prove that corrective feedback is easier to embrace if you are in a good self-regulatory state and not tired or upset. Candidness is a crucial part of building trust. If you are able to notice something valuable that a person could improve on, it means you care.</description></item><item><title>Building Deeper Connections with Others</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/in-depth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/in-depth/</guid><description>In a fast-paced world filled with distractions and superficial interactions, engaging in meaningful conversations has become a rare occurrence. With colleagues, family, friends, and even strangers, the ability to engage in deep, authentic conversations is a skill worth honing. Meaningful conversations not only foster stronger relationships but also provide opportunities for personal growth and understanding. Here are some tips to help you cultivate meaningful conversations in various aspects of your life.</description></item><item><title>Creating value for your remote team</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/anchors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/anchors/</guid><description>Being an effective remote manager is tricky. You have to find the right leadership style that corresponds to your personal values, take care of your team, and make sure that you hit the goals that are important for the business.
When juggling between all the tasks you have on your plate when leading a remote workforce, it’s important to pay attention to the things that are important for the people you manage.</description></item><item><title>Leading a team remotely</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/leading/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/leading/</guid><description>How to make work a better place for your virtual team While all of us come to work every day for various reasons, there are several universal things that make remote work better. In remote teams, leaders have the opportunity to create an environment in which a team can flourish by building a sense of competency, autonomy, and relatedness for everyone. When people feel that they are competent in what they are doing, that they have a choice of tasks and independence, and that somebody at work cares about them, they feel happier, grow better professionally, and feel more engaged with their jobs.</description></item><item><title>Managing team members based on their competency levels</title><link>https://hygge.work/blog/situational-leadership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/blog/situational-leadership/</guid><description>Situational leadership and how to use it in onboarding and day-to-day team management
Leadership is not a one-size-fits-all approach. A leader comes across various types of people and situations, and that’s where situational leadership comes into the picture—it’s all about tailoring your leadership style to fit the situation and the competency level of your team members.
When it comes to leadership styles, there are four main types: directing, coaching, supporting, and delegating.</description></item></channel></rss>